<class>
    <room>
        <name>IntroArcade</name>
        <description>Where the player first enters the game</description>
        <story_text>, you are a huge fan of "old-skool" video games. You walk into your favorite arcade and find an old dusty machine that you've never seen before. It looks just like the other gaming machines, except that it's powered off.

        You find the power plug and plug it into a nearby wall socket. The device flickers to life, and strange sounds garble and warp around you. The screen is on but dark with no apparent logos or company brands.

        A small slot is found below the controllers. You get a weird feeling as you reach into your pocket to pull out your quarter... Do you put your quarter into the slot?</story_text>
        <visible_buttons>2</visible_buttons>
        <btn1_text>Yes</btn1_text>
        <btn2_text>No</btn2_text>
        <btn3_text></btn3_text>
        <c1>StartingPoint0</c1>
        <c2>StartingPoint0.5</c2>
        <c3></c3>
    </room>
<!--    <room>-->
<!--        <name>StartingPoint0.5</name>-->
<!--        <description>You said no to the game</description>-->
<!--        <story_text>As you reach down your pockets to pick up your quarter. Your quarter falls down the slot.-->
<!--        </story_text>-->
<!--        <visible_buttons>1</visible_buttons>-->
<!--        <btn1_text>You feel strange!</btn1_text>-->
<!--        <c1>StartingPoint0</c1>-->
<!--    </room>-->
    <room>
        <name>StartingPoint0</name>
        <description>Starting point when the player first enters the pixelated world</description>
        <story_text>Feeling gypped of a quarter, you turn around to walk towards the customer service desk and you can't believe your eyes. All void. You completely spin 360 degrees, look up, then down. Only darkness surrounds you.

        All of a sudden, a light begins to glow several meters ahead. You walk towards the light--your only chance to discover how you got here...

        A single ball of light lays on the floor in front of you. You reach out to pick it up, and you notice that your arms are distorted! You look down at your body and legs--you can't believe what you see--you're completely pixelated!

        You grab the light, and it begins to hover around your head. It seems to be providing the light you need to see anything within the darkness.

        You think to yourself: "How do I get out of here?" Your basic surival logic kicks in, and you begin to look around for answers. You're currently standing in the room where you found the mysterious light. Instead of getting lost in the dark, you attempt to try basic movement patterns first.

        Where do you want to go?</story_text>
        <visible_buttons>3</visible_buttons>
        <btn1_text>Go left</btn1_text>
        <btn2_text>Go right</btn2_text>
        <btn3_text>Go forward</btn3_text>
        <c1>GreenPath1</c1>
        <c2>PurplePath1</c2>
        <c3>GoldPath1</c3>
    </room>
    <room>
        <name>StartingPoint</name>
        <description>Starting point once the player revisits the area after already being in the game</description>
        <story_text>You're back where you first found yourself after entering the void.

        Where do you want to go?</story_text>
        <visible_buttons>3</visible_buttons>
        <btn1_text>Go left</btn1_text>
        <btn2_text>Go right</btn2_text>
        <btn3_text>Go forward</btn3_text>
        <c1>GreenPath1</c1>
        <c2>PurplePath1</c2>
        <c3>GoldPath1</c3>
    </room>
    <room>
        <name>ExitDoor</name>
        <description>Exit door before both keys are acquired</description>
        <story_text>A large, pixelated golden door appears in front of you. It has two key slots.

        It looks like you don't have what you need to unlock the door.</story_text>
        <visible_buttons>1</visible_buttons>
        <btn1_text>Head back toward your starting point</btn1_text>
        <btn2_text></btn2_text>
        <btn3_text></btn3_text>
        <c1>GoldPath2</c1>
        <c2></c2>
        <c3></c3>
    </room>
    <room>
        <name>ExitDoorWin</name>
        <description>Exit door after both keys are acquired</description>
        <story_text>A large, pixelated golden door appears in front of you. It has two key slots.

        You place both keys into the slots, turn them, and hear a distinct click. You push open the door, and a bright white light blinds you. You rub your eyes, and when you open them, you are staring at the screen of the mysterious machine in the arcade. This time, the screen is now showing Frogger and Snake working as usual. You hear a coin drop below into the coin return panel. You grab the coin and look at it. This is the quarter you used to pay for the game, however one side of the quarter displays a glitched Frogger and the other side displays a glitched Snake. YOU WIN!!</story_text>
        <visible_buttons>0</visible_buttons>
        <btn1_text></btn1_text>
        <btn2_text></btn2_text>
        <btn3_text></btn3_text>
        <c1></c1>
        <c2></c2>
        <c3></c3>
    </room>
    <room>
        <name>SnakeTerminal</name>
        <description>MiniGame that gives key upon completion before you earn key</description>
        <story_text>A small, neon purple gaming terminal appears in front of you. It looks exactly like a normal arcade game, but pixelated. On the screen appears a familiar theme--a long snake eating a block, however the snake's body looks distorted. There are controllers beneath the screen.

        After grabbing the controllers, you hear the same sounds that warped all around you before! You close your eyes in fear, and when you open them you see a familiar block in the distance. The snake is nowhere to be seen! You take one step forward to get a better look and you slither! Looking down in disbelief, you are completely purple. You have become the snake!</story_text>
        <visible_buttons>0</visible_buttons>
        <btn1_text></btn1_text>
        <btn2_text></btn2_text>
        <btn3_text></btn3_text>
        <c1></c1>
        <c2></c2>
        <c3></c3>
    </room>
    <room>
        <name>SnakeTerminalMid</name>
        <description>Place to go while the player's results of the game are not yet determined</description>
        <story_text>...You are playing Snake...

            Win or Lose to be able to go back to the hall.</story_text>
        <visible_buttons>0</visible_buttons>
        <btn1_text></btn1_text>
        <btn2_text></btn2_text>
        <btn3_text></btn3_text>
        <c1></c1>
        <c2></c2>
        <c3></c3>
    </room>
    <room>
        <name>SnakeTerminalEnd</name>
        <description>MiniGame that gives key upon completion after you earn key</description>
        <story_text>Finish gathering your points from Snake before you even decide to go back to the starting point.</story_text>
        <visible_buttons>1</visible_buttons>
        <btn1_text>Head back toward your starting point</btn1_text>
        <btn2_text></btn2_text>
        <btn3_text></btn3_text>
        <c1>StartingPoint</c1>
        <c2></c2>
        <c3></c3>
    </room>
    <room>
        <name>FroggerTerminal</name>
        <description>MiniGame that gives key upon completion before you earn key</description>
        <story_text>A small, neon green gaming terminal appears in front of you. It looks exactly like a normal arcade game, but pixelated. On the screen appears a familiar theme--a small frog crossing a busy road, however the frog looksdistorted. There are controllers beneath the screen. 

        What do you want to do?</story_text>
        <visible_buttons>0</visible_buttons>
        <btn1_text></btn1_text>
        <btn2_text></btn2_text>
        <btn3_text></btn3_text>
        <c1></c1>
        <c2></c2>
        <c3></c3>
    </room>
    <room>
        <name>FroggerTerminalEnd</name>
        <description>MiniGame that gives key upon completion after you earn key</description>
        <story_text>I would hate to see you cross a real street the way you were dodging vehicles. It looks like the glitch has been fixed.

        What do you want to do now?</story_text>
        <visible_buttons>1</visible_buttons>
        <btn1_text>Head back toward your starting point</btn1_text>
        <btn2_text></btn2_text>
        <btn3_text></btn3_text>
        <c1>GreenPath2</c1>
        <c2></c2>
        <c3></c3>
    </room>
    <room>
        <name>PurplePath1</name>
        <description>Empty room</description>
        <story_text>You see a faint glimpse of purple light in the distance.</story_text>
        <visible_buttons>2</visible_buttons>
        <btn1_text>Keep going toward the purple light</btn1_text>
        <btn2_text>Head back to your starting point</btn2_text>
        <btn3_text></btn3_text>
        <c1>PurplePath2</c1>
        <c2>StartingPoint</c2>
        <c3></c3>
    </room>
    <room>
        <name>PurplePath2</name>
        <description>Empty room</description>
        <story_text>The purple light grows brighter.</story_text>
        <visible_buttons>2</visible_buttons>
        <btn1_text>Keep going to the purple light</btn1_text>
        <btn2_text>Head back toward your starting point</btn2_text>
        <btn3_text></btn3_text>
        <c1>SnakeTerminal</c1>
        <c2>PurplePath1</c2>
        <c3></c3>
    </room>
    <room>
        <name>GreenPath1</name>
        <description>Empty room</description>
        <story_text>You see a faint glimpse of green light in the distance.</story_text>
        <visible_buttons>2</visible_buttons>
        <btn1_text>Keep going toward the green light</btn1_text>
        <btn2_text>Head back to your starting point</btn2_text>
        <btn3_text></btn3_text>
        <c1>GreenPath2</c1>
        <c2>StartingPoint</c2>
        <c3></c3>
    </room>
    <room>
        <name>GreenPath2</name>
        <description>Empty room</description>
        <story_text>The green light grows brighter.</story_text>
        <visible_buttons>2</visible_buttons>
        <btn1_text>Keep going to the green light</btn1_text>
        <btn2_text>Head back toward your starting point</btn2_text>
        <btn3_text></btn3_text>
        <c1>FroggerTerminal</c1>
        <c2>GreenPath1</c2>
        <c3></c3>
    </room>
    <room>
        <name>GoldPath1</name>
        <description>Empty room</description>
        <story_text>You see a faint glimpse of gold light in the distance.</story_text>
        <visible_buttons>2</visible_buttons>
        <btn1_text>Keep going toward the gold light</btn1_text>
        <btn2_text>Head back to your starting point</btn2_text>
        <btn3_text></btn3_text>
        <c1>GoldPath2</c1>
        <c2>StartingPoint</c2>
        <c3></c3>
    </room>
    <room>
        <name>GoldPath2</name>
        <description>Empty room</description>
        <story_text>The gold light grows brighter</story_text>
        <visible_buttons>2</visible_buttons>
        <btn1_text>Keep going to the gold light</btn1_text>
        <btn2_text>Head back toward your starting point</btn2_text>
        <btn3_text></btn3_text>
        <c1>ExitDoor</c1>
        <c2>GoldPath1</c2>
        <c3></c3>
    </room>
</class>